Finding Aid for the Lewis MacAdams papers LSC.2289
UCLA Library Special Collections
Lewis MacAdams papers
1944-2014
UCLA Library Special Collections
MacAdams, Lewis
LSC.2289
53.2 linear feet (121 boxes, 5 half boxes, 2 flat boxes, 2 flat boxes oversize, 1 telescoping box)
Lewis MacAdams is a Los Angeles-based poet, journalist, and filmmaker, and has authored over 20 books of poems and stories. Collection materials include MacAdams' monographs; environmental and cultural journalism; film projects; correspondence with poets and artists; files related to the Friends of the Los Angeles River (FoLAR); performance materials from the San Francisco and Los Angeles poetry and arts scenes; publications from MacAdams' library, and personal memorabilia, as well as countless drafts and poetry fragments. MacAdams' work embraces performance art and political activism on behalf of local and national causes, and includes files related to the founding of FoLAR. His writings about the river, politics, culture, and crime have been published in Rolling Stone, the Los Angeles Times, and the L.A. Weekly.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: This collection contains both processed and unprocessed audiovisual materials. For information about the access status of the material that you are looking for, refer to the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note at the series and file levels. All requests to access processed audiovisual materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Donated by Lewis MacAdams, 2015.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9981095623606533
Biography/History
Lewis MacAdams is a poet, journalist, and filmmaker whose work embraces performance art and political activism. Born October 12, 1944 and raised in Dallas, Texas, MacAdams earned a B.A. in English from Princeton in 1966 and a Master's degree from State University of New York, Buffalo in 1968. He participated in the poetry and performance scenes in Bolinas and San Francisco and was director of the Poetry Center at San Francisco State University from 1975-1978. After moving to Los Angeles, MacAdams concentrated on poetry and journalism as well as film and television projects, including a collaboration with EZTV founder John Dorr and the Lannan Foundation on a video series that featured readings by poets. He also wrote and performed with avant-garde artists like The Dark Bob and others in the Los Angeles performance scene. MacAdams founded Friends of the Los Angeles River (FOLAR) in 1986, which he describes as a "40-year art work" that aims to harness creative energies which engage politics, magic, and imagination "to bring the Los Angeles River, one of the most degraded rivers on earth, back to life." MacAdams has been married twice and has four children.
Scope and Content
Collection materials include MacAdams' writings such as monographs, journalism, and film projects, correspondence with poets and artists, files related to the Friends of the Los Angeles River, performance materials and fliers from the Los Angeles poetry and art scenes, publications from MacAdams' library, and memorabilia. Materials also include interviews and transcripts for his book The Birth of The Cool: Beat, Bebop, and the American Avant-Garde about the cultural history of the idea of cool, and materials related to his unpublished biography of Rolling Stone magazine founder Jann Wenner. This collection contains scripts for television and film projects, including material related to his documentary What Happened to Kerouac? and other video projects in collaboration with EZTV founder John Dorr, as well as a near-complete run of WET magazine, for which MacAdams was editor from 1980-1982. Audiovisual materials include interviews by MacAdams, television and movie projects, and performances.
Organization and Arrangement
This collection has been arranged in the following series based on preservation of the existing order and the imposition of an intellectual order:
1. Writing by MacAdams
2. Correspondence
3. FoLAR files
4. Performance materials
5. Publications
6. Memorabilia
Related Material
Friends of the Los Angeles River records, 1987-2013 (Collection 2215). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles.
Alexandra Garrett Papers and Records of the Beyond Baroque Foundation, 1965-1991 (Collection 1615). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles.
Aram Saroyan Papers, 1965-1989 (Collection 991). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles.
Wanda Coleman papers, 1960-2013 (Collection 2282). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles.
Allan H. Kurtzman Collection of Material about Beat Writers and Artists, ca. 1950-1989 (Collection 362). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles.
Metadata Rights Declaration
Finding aid description and metadata in this record are licensed under a Creative Commons Public Domain Designation (CC0 1.0 Universal). See LSC's Metadata Rights Statement for more information.
Civic leaders -- California -- Los Angeles -- Archives.; Authors, American -- 20th century -- Archives.; Friends of the Los Angeles River; MacAdams, Lewis -- Archives
- Writing by MacAdams
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  COLLECTION CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. All requests to access special collections material must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  COLLECTION CONTAINS DIGITAL MATERIALS: Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. All requests to access special collections material must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  - Poetry (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Folder 1)
    SUBSERIES CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. All requests to access special collections material must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
    Box 6, Folder 3: One Dear Oxygen CD featuring Lewis MacAdams and The Dark Bob.
    Scope and Content
    The poetry subseries includes poems by MacAdams written on a spectrum of surfaces.
    Box 1 includes a folder of his resumes and biographies.
    Boxes 6-8 include monographs by MacAdams.
    Books from Lewis MacAdams' library that were originally donated with the papers have been individually cataloged in the UCLA Library online catalog. Records for these items may be found by searching the Special Coll/Archive SPAC "LMAC" using the Advanced search tab in the Library catalog, or keyword searching "Books from the Library of Lewis MacAdams."
  - Birth Of The Cool (Box 9, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Box 18)
    Box 18: One CD, 3 VHS tapes, and 5 audio cassettes.
    Box 18: Thirteen 3.5" floppy disks.
    This subseries includes notes, manuscripts, research materials, interviews, publicity files, royalty statements, photographs, and proofs related to his book Birth Of The Cool: Beat, Bebop, and the American Avant Garde.
    Box 12 includes a partially smoked marijuana joint.
    Box 13 contains photo research materials including correspondence, illustrations, negatives, photographs, and permissions.
    Box 18 includes interviews with Judith Malina, Fielding Dawson, Allen Ginsberg, Robert F. Kennedy Jr., and Lewis MacAdams. MacAdams discusses the book, the notion of how cool was an act of defiance starting amongst post-World War II African American Jazz musicians and how it spread to the cultural mainstream. This box also contains book chapters on floppy disks, a Birth Of The Cool MTV2 News segment, and a John Coltrane documentary.
  - Jann Wenner Biography (Box 19, Box 20, Box 21, Box 22, Box 23, Box 24, Box 25, Box 26, Box 27, Box 28, Box 29, Box 30, Box 31, Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Box 35, Box 36)
    Box 24: One CD, two VHS, twenty-two microcassettes, and fifty-one Minidiscs.
    Box 25: Nine VHS and 5 CDs.
    Box 34: One CD and 1 DVD.
    Box 28, folder 2: One 3.5" floppy disk.
    Box 32, folder 1: One 3.5" floppy disk.
    The Jann Wenner Biography subseries includes drafts, notes, correspondence, research files, interviews, transcripts, and monographs collected from the Wenner family.
    Boxes 19-20 contain notes, questions, drafts, correspondence, and interview transcripts for the following: Jann Wenner, Kent Brownridge, Christine Doudna, Sarah Lazin, and Yoko Ono.
    Box 21 contains notes and interview transcripts for Dallas Clark, David Felton, Merlyn Wenner Ruddell, and Sim Wenner. This box also includes a research files on Hunter S. Thompson and early Rolling Stone articles.
    Boxes 22-23 contain notes, transcripts, drafts and correspondence with, Jann, Sim, and Kate Wenner. Box 22 includes a copy of Chester White Flippo's thesis Rock Journalism and Rolling Stone.
    Box 24 includes a MTV News Special Report on Hate Rock, a MTV News Straight Dope Special Report On Drugs, and interviews with the following: Jann Wenner, Annie Leibovitz, Kent Brownridge, Sarah Lazin, Bob Wallace, Ahmet Ertegun, Mike Salisbury, Marianne Partridge, Elizabeth Schmidt, Charles M. Young, Cindy Ehrlich, Jac Holzman, Michael Douglas, Don Henley, Baron Wolman, Tom Wolfe, Juan Thompson, Yoko Ono, Jackson Browne, Sim Wenner, Clive Davis, Chet Helms, Dallas Clark, Merlyn Wenner Ruddell, Kate Wenner, and Laurel Gonsalves.
    Box 25 includes Jann Wenner interviews, Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum (RRHOFAM) speeches, RRHOFAM opening weekend highlights, Vision & Triumph: How Cleveland Built the Rock Hall, Rolling Stone interview with Hunter S. Thompson, Rap with Ben Fong-Torres, Al Green Visits Rolling Stone, and "TVTV covers Rolling Stone 16mm Edition Show as it appeared on NET SHOW BEHIND THE LINES."
    Box 26: Chapter drafts and Hunter S. Thompson memorial materials.
    Box 27: Research files, drafts, notes, Kurt Loder file, and correspondence with Jamie Moran.
    Box 28: Drafts and notes.
    Box 29 contains RRHOFAM materials, a contacts file, correspondence, contracts, notes, and chapter drafts.
    Box 30: RRHOFAM research file, chapter outlines, drafts, and notes.
    Box 31 includes business cards, notes, drafts, Andrew Wylie emails, and Annie Leibovitz files.
    Box 32: Drafts, book proposal, chapter outlines, and synopsis of the Wenner biography titled Jann Wenner and his Time.
    Box 33: Drafts, outlines, notes, and research materials.
    Box 34: Chapter drafts, notes, and an Rolling Stone ex-employee reunion file which includes an RSX Stories CD and the RSX Antacid Flashback DVD.
    Box 35: Monographs by Sim Wenner, Kate Wenner, and Margaret Lee Chadwick.
    Box 36: Margaret Lee Chadwick's Chadwick School yearbooks 1959-1964.
  - Journalism (Box 37, Box 38, Box 39, Box 40, Box 41, Box 42, Box 43, Box 44, Box 45, Box 46, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49, Box 50, Box 51, Box 52, Box 53, Box 54, Box 55, Box 56, Box 57)
    Box 39, folder 14: One 3.5" floppy disk - Complete L.A. Weekly Files as of June 1994.
    Box 39, folder 15: Three 3.5" floppy disks of articles and proposals for Rolling Stone and L.A. Times Magazine.
    Box 41: One MiniDisc, and four 5.25" floppy disks that contain the following titles: Love Stories, Show Coalition, Mother Jones, Rest of the Story, L.A. Suspicions, Harvard School, John Dorr, Poetry Championships, Jesse Jackson, and Resume.
    Box 41: Ten audio cassettes.
    The Journalism subseries includes article proposals, notes, research materials, audio recordings, interview transcripts, drafts, clippings, and periodicals.
    Box 37 includes the following files: Friends of Mark Nathanson, World Heavyweight Poetry Championship, Pot Wars, Jeremiah of the Palms, History of the Sunset Strip, On Burroughs Work, and Love Conquers Zen.
    Box 38 contains the following files: Buddhist Things, Zen Biz, Notre Dame of Buddhism, Robert Smithson Biography, Anjelica Houston, Tilth, Johnny Rotten, Jackie Goldberg, MOCA, John Milius, Robert Mitchum, Suzanne, Lacy, and Ed Sanders.
    Box 39 includes files for Urban Coyote, Sunshine Muse, The Ambassador from E.L.A., "The Rookie," "Selling of L.A. County," "How is the Sailboat Art?," L.A. Weekly, "Blendo Manifesto," and WET Magazine. Folder 1 contains his "Ode to Sylvester" and folder 14 includes his L.A. Weekly Reporter's Notebook.
    Box 40 includes "Blendo Manifesto," "Truckstop Portraits," and "The 710 Split."
    Box 41 includes recordings on audio cassette of Timothy Leary, Cassandra Wilson, Kim Jones, Joe Biroc, R.D. Laing, Hal Ezell, Steve Gibson, and Thom Mount as well as articles on floppy discs.
    - ? poesia. Bologna., 1981 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - 3+3: A Reading of 6 Los Angeles Poets. Los Angeles., circa 2008 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - 3+3: A Reading of Six Los Angeles Poets. Los Angeles., circa 2008 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - 432 Review, no. 2. New York., 1976 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - 432 Review, no. 3. New York., 1976 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - 432 Review, no. 4. New York., 1976 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - 432 Review, no. 5. New York., 1977 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - 432 Review, no. 7. New York., 1978 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - 4 Taxis, no. 1. Bordeaux., 1981 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - 4 Taxis, no. 8. Bordeaux., 1981-1982 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - 4 Taxis, no. 9-10. Bordeaux., 1984 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - A Directory of American Poets. New York., 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - A Hundred Posters, no. 14. Boston., 1977 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - A Hundred Posters, no. 21. Boston., 1977 September (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - ACTS, v. 1, no. 2. San Francisco., 1983 June (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Actuel, no. 5. Paris., 1980 March (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Actuel, no. 15. Paris., 1981 January (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Actuel, no. 16. Paris., 1981 February (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Actuel, no. 21-22. Paris., 1981 July-August (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Actuel, no. 23. Paris., 1981 September (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Adventures in Poetry, no. 11. Brooklyn., 1974 Spring (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - All Ways Free. Eugene., 1993 Summer (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Am Here Books: Catalogue 6. Santa Barbara., circa 1982 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - American Poetry Archive, second series. San Francisco., 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - American Poetry Archive, third series. San Francisco., 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - The American Poetry Archive: Circulating Videotape Library. San Francisco., 1974-1982 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - The American Poetry Archives: Videotape Catalogue. San Francisco., 1974-1990 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - The Archive Newsletter. La Jolla., 1983 Fall (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Arroyo Arts Collective, v. 11, no. 6. Highland Park., 2000 November-December (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Arshile, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1993 Spring (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Art & Antiques, no. 1. New York., 1984 March (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Art & Antiques. New York., 1984 May (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Art & Antiques. New York., 1984 September (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Art & Antiques. New York., 1984 October (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Artlines. Taos., 1985 June (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Atari Connection, v. 4, no. 2. Taos., 1984 Summer (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Attaboy!, no. 1. Boulder., 1976 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Avalanche. New York., 1974 December (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Avalanche. New York., 1975 Summer (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Avalanche. New York., 1975 Winter (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Barney. Venice., 1981 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Beyond Baroque Magazine, v. 26, no. 2. Venice., 2004 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Big Sky, no. 9. Bolinas., 1975 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Big Sky, no. 10. Bolinas., 1976 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - BLITZ, no. 58. London., 1987 October (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Blue Book, no. 2. San Francisco., 1999 April (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Blue Book, no. 3. San Francisco., 1999 June (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Blue Book, no. 7. Palo Alto., 2002 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Bombay Gin, no. 4. Boulder., 1977 Summer-Fall (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Bombay Gin, no. 6. Boulder., 1978 Summer-1979 Spring (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Buddhist Peace Fellowship Newsletter. Berkeley., 1990 Spring (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - C: A Journal of Poetry, v. 1, no. 2. New York., 1963 June (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - C: A Journal of Poetry, v. 1, no. 4. New York., 1963 September (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - C: A Journal of Poetry, v. 1, no. 7. New York., 1964 February (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - California Magazine, v. 7, no. 3. Beverly Hills., 1982 March (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - California Magazine, v. 8, no. 11. Beverly Hills., 1983 November (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - California Magazine, v. 8, no. 12. Beverly Hills., 1983 December (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - California Magazine, v. 9, no. 1. Beverly Hills., 1984 January (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - California Magazine, v. 9, no. 3. Beverly Hills., 1984 March (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - California, v. 13, no. 3. Los Angeles., 1988 March (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - California, v. 13, no. 7. Los Angeles., 1988 July (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - California Coast & Ocean, v. 18, no. 1. Oakland., 2002 Spring (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - California Waterfront Age, v. 6, no. 1. Oakland., 1990 Winter-Spring (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - California Democratic Convention. Los Angeles., 1986 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Cat In The Wind. Pleasant Hill., 1976 May (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Chicago, v. 2, nos. 2 & 3. Chicago., 1976 March-April (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - CITY Magazine International, no. 18. Paris., 1986 January (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Cleavon Little's Magazine, no. 1., 2000 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Coagula Art Journal, no. 22. Huntington Park., 1996 Summer (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Coagula Art Journal, no. 28. Huntington Park., 1997 Summer (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - The CoEvolution Quarterly, no. 12. Sausalito., 1976-1977 Winter (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - The CoEvolution Quarterly, no. 14. Sausalito., 1977 Summer (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - The CoEvolution Quarterly, no. 17. Sausalito., 1978 Spring (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Colibri, no. 1. Napoli., 1979 January (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Colin's Magazine, no. 2. Seattle., 1991 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Compost Files, no. 1. Bolinas., 1980 Fall (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Cornerstones, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1980 November (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Cornerstones, no. 2. Los Angeles., 1981 January-February (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Coyote's Journal, no. 8. San Francisco., 1967 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Daily News Magazine. Los Angeles., 1984 October 28 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - The Dane. Colorado Springs., 1974 December 18 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Dazed and Confused, v. 3, no. 11. London., 2012 July (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - The Democratic Times, v. 1, no. 3. San Francisco., 1986 Winter (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Den Del's Devil's Gate Auto Repair Magazine. Boulder. Palo Alto., 2002 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Detour. Boulder. Los Angeles., 1994 January-February (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Digraphe, no. 20. Paris., 1979 September (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Di Versi In Versi. Parma., 1984 November (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - East Village Eye. New York., 1986 June (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - eggs, v. 1, no. 1. Princeton., 1964 May (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Emigre, no. 1. Berkeley., 1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Emigre, no. 2. Berkeley., 1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Emigre, no. 3. Berkeley., 1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - L'Europeo, no. 25. Milan., circa 1970s (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Evergreen Review, v. 2, no. 6. New York., 1958 Autumn (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Evergreen Review, v. 3, no. 10. New York., 1959 November-December (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Evergreen Review, v. 5, no. 19. New York., 1961 July-August (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Exquisite Corpse, v. 1, no. 4. Baltimore., 1983 April (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Exquisite Corpse, v. 1, no. 12. Baltimore., 1983 December (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Exquisite Corpse, v. 2, no. 1. Baltimore., 1984 January-February (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Exquisite Corpse, v. 2, no. 3-4. Baltimore., 1984 March-April (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Exquisite Corpse, v. 2, no. 5-7. Baltimore., 1984 May-July (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Exquisite Corpse, v. 4, no. 1-2. Baton Rouge., 1986 January-February (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Exquisite Corpse, v. 4, no. 5-8. Baton Rouge., 1986 May-August (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Exquisite Corpse, v. 5, nos. 1-5. Baton Rouge., 1987 January-May (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Exquisite Corpse, no. 37. Baton Rouge., 1992 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Exquisite Corpse, no. 55. Baton Rouge., 1995 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - The Face, no. 90. London., 1987 October (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Garuda, no. 1. Barnet. Boulder., 1971 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Garuda, no. 3. Boulder. Berkeley., 1973 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Gas, no. 1. San Francisco., 1990 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Gas, no. 2. San Carlos., 1991 Spring (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Gas, no. 4. San Carlos., 1991-1992 Winter (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Gas, no. 5. San Carlos., 1993 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Gas, no. 6. Palo Alto., 1994-1995 Winter (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Gas, no. 8. Palo Alto., 1996-1997 Winter (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Gas, no. 9. Palo Alto., 1997 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Gas, no. 10. Palo Alto., 1997-1998 Winter-Spring (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Gate Magazine, no. 4. Rohrhof., 1995 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Gazette of the Grolier Club, no. 51. New York., 2000 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - The Great Western Pacific Coastal Post, v. 4, no. 36. Bolinas., 1979 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Hard Werken, no. 10. Rotterdam., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - High Country. Angel Fire., 1999 Summer (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - High Performance, v. 3, no. 3 and 4, issue 11/12. Los Angeles., 1980 Fall-Winter (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - High Performance, v. 4, no. 3, issue 15. Los Angeles., 1981 Fall (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - High Performance, v. 5, no. 4, issue 20. Los Angeles., 1983 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - High Performance, v. 6, no. 4, issue 24. Los Angeles., 1983 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - High Performance, v. 7, no. 1, issue 25. Los Angeles., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - High Performance, v. 7, no. 3, issue 27. Los Angeles., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - High Performance, v. 7, no. 4, issue 28. Los Angeles., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - High Performance, v. 13, no. 2, issue 50. Santa Monica., 1990 Summer (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - The Hollywood Reporter, v. 275, no. 29. Hollywood., 1985 January 31 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - The Hollywood Review, no. 1. Santa Monica., 1991 Spring (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - intent., v. 1, no. 1. Buffalo., 1989 Spring (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - intent., v. 2, no. 1. Buffalo., 1990 Late Spring (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - In The Light. Barrington., 1975 August (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - ISSUE, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1983 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - KPFA FOLIO, v. 28, issue 5. Berkeley., 1977 May (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Kulchur, v. 3, no. 9. New York., 1963 Spring (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Kulchur, v. 5, no. 17. New York., 1965 Spring (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Kulchur, v. 5, no. 20. New York., 1965-1966 Winter (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - L.A. Weekly 20. Los Angeles., 1998 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - L.A. Style, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1985 June (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - L.A. Style, v. 2, no. 4. Los Angeles., 1986 September (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Little Horse's Magazine. Boulder., 2004 Spring (Box 50, Folder 3)